

Personal information



ophelia.m.aguilar@gmail.com (+46)760-070035

Vasavägen 24 Solna, Stockholm

Skills

C#

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Java

Kotlin

React.js

React Native

Swift

UI

UX

Figma

UML

Scrum

Vue.js

Tailwind CSS

Languages

Swedish - Native

English - Fluent

Social media







Ophelia Aguilar

Programming Student

Summary

I'm a 25-year-old programming student looking for new opportunities in Stockholm.

I'm currently studying app development at Stockholms Tekniska Institut. In the spring I'll be graduating as a full-fledged programmer.

I'm a hard worker, curious, and open to everything new. I would like to have the opportunity to learn and contribute by working alongside you.

Education

App Development

2021 - 2023

Stockholms Tekniska Institut

The studies are mainly focused on mobile app development. I've also studied project management, UX, UI, and how to build prototypes in Figma.

2020 - 2021 Programming

Kvinnofolkhögskolan

I studied the fundamentals of programming. I frequently used UML for projects and used Scrum to sufficiently plan a wedding with a group of classmates.

2015 - 2016 Society & Behavioral Science

Birkagårdens Folkhögskola

2013 - 2015 Art & Design

Cybergymnasiet

Work experience

Programming Intern

January 2023 - April 2023

Capacio AB

I mainly focused on building and improving their website and design, using React.js, Vue.js, Tailwind CSS and Figma.

Warehouse Worker

April 2022 - September 2022

Mopedrenovering

Claims Adjuster

Programming Intern

April 2021 - May 2021

February 2020 - July 2020

Albert Schapiro Autonomo

I mainly focused on building and improving their website, using React.js

AmTrust Insurance Services Sweden

October 2019 - January 2020 Sales Advisor

H&M

Customer Service Employee & Insurance Agent **August 2018 – April 2019**

mySafety Försäkringar

July 2016 - August 2018 Additional work experience

I worked as a Barista and Restaurant Staff at MAX Hamburgare, Espresso House, and Burger

King.

